Now, I know we're going long here, but this, we couldn't pry this pick out of here.
This is the best pick of my life. I have never, ever had a better pick on this show, ever.
Till next week.
I don't know what I'm going to do. I haven't fully incorporated how I'm going to change
my life around this pick, but I'm beginning to experiment with it, maybe like something
on my phone, something on a laptop, and I got to have like something in VR. So, friends,
I want to tell you about, now, I know this is not going to be a big deal for everybody,
but it's very special to me. I want to tell you about Cliparr. Cliparr is a streamlined
media clipper that allows you to quickly create and download clips from what is currently
playing via Plex or Jellyfin. No way. Say a guy is watching King of the Hill on his TV,
he can pull this page up, and if you hit clip, it will grab just a little handle before the
moment you hit clip, and about 20 seconds after you hit clip. And it brings it up in
what is perhaps the best web interface I've ever seen for editing clips, and I've played
with a lot of them. It includes the transcript if the file has it, it pulls it right from
your Jellyfin or Plex server, and then you can, it has a way to trim it like a standard
linear video editor, you can trim the clip to what you want, and it has a bunch of great
export options to export just that clip. And it works so great. You can also expand beyond
what it clipped. So like if what with a region you wanted was earlier or later, you just expand
the clip and it has the entire file. You can also link MP4 files that are on an HTTP endpoint
or upload video files to it. But for me, there's been so many times when I'm watching something
and I'm like, I would love to play a clip of that on the show, or that would make a great
boost sound bite. Or there's been so many times I've been like, I wish audience members could
send us some great boost soundboard bites. And this way you can just be watching something.
If somebody says something that would make a great clip or something or a ringtone or
whatever, you just hit the button and it grabs a clip of it. Like I was watching Futurama
last night and this just, and I'm like, oh, and I just hit the button. Blockchain's not
the boss of me. I'm like, I gotta have that. Right? I just hit the button and then I just
trim it a little bit. Blockchain's not the boss of me. And I've got it now. I've got
it now. We've been asking for this ever since the boost sort of thing, basically. Yeah. Or
anytime you could play sounds or if you want like funny clips from a movie or if you and
your friends love a scene or something like that, or you want to share something from
a great episode over a messaging app. I mean, it goes on and on buddy. It's so good. It's
so good. It can burn in the subtitles if you want. It pulls from your existing media. Just
five months old it looks like all of the work. Like if there's any transcoding work required,
it's all done in the browser. Wow. It's this is impressive. It's really, really good. And
it's MIT licensed. Is there anything that's not so great about it? Like, I mean, you know,
it's new and so it's going to be, it's not a hundred percent. Like one time I went to
clip, I think it was a movie and it just brought the whole thing into the timeline, but then
it was really easy to just mark it in and out and just drop it. And so that was great. Nice.
And then you got, I haven't tried just uploading the local file, but they offer that. I'm so
happy. I'm so, so, so happy. It's so good. It's so good. It was so easy to set up too.
Oh, I have a question. You have recently when you so choose to do this manually, been taking
like a Dolby 5.1 channel audio and then like selecting the very specific channel you want.
Is that capable here yet? Or is that a feature? I don't think so. But I, one time I did bring
in a clip and I did see multiple tracks and I didn't poke around to see if some of them
were audio, but I don't think it does that. What you're saying is like, if you, if you're,
if you open up like something that surrounds and you grab just the center center channel,
that's almost always the dialogue mostly isolated. So it gets rid of someone like the background
music or sound effects and you get mostly just the dialogue, which is really a neat trick.
Oh gosh, Cliparr, Cliparr. So happy. So happy.